Guide to the Herman Haupt Chapman Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- VOLUMES, 1881-1956; Series I; 23.25 linear feet (53 boxes)
  - Volume No: 24A Grazing vs. Pine in Southwest; Westveld: Sheep Damage, 1919-1932 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Volume No: 25 Grazing: Southwest, 1908-1937 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Volume No: 25A Grazing: National Forests, 1920-1954 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Volume No: 25B Grazing: Correspondence, 1927-1953 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Volume No: 26 Jackson Lumber Company: Data, 1945-1951 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Volume No: 27 Jackson Lumber Company: Management, 1946-1951 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Volume No: 28 Jackson Lumber Company: Reappraisal, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Volume No: 29 Society of American Foresters: Canons of Ethics, 1946-1950 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Volume No: 30 Society of American Foresters: Oregon and California Lands; Standards of Membership, 1933-1947 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Volume No: 31 Society of American Foresters: Regulation of Private Forests, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Volume No: 32 U.S. Department of the Interior: Oregon and California Land Grants, 1936-1952 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Volume No: 33 Jackson Lumber Company: Reports, 1939-1951 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Volume No: 34 Papers, 1939-1955 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Volume No: 35 Papers, 1950-1955 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Volume No: 36A Connecticut State Parks: Histories B-H (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Volume No: 36B Connecticut State Parks: Histories H-W (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Volume No: 37 Connecticut: Sherwood Island, 1915-1953 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Volume No: 38 Connecticut State Forests: A-T (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Volume No: 39 Connecticut Forest and Park Commissions and Private Organizations, 1932-1956 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Volume No: 40 Connecticut Commission on Forests and Wildlife (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Policies, 1919-1945 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Civilian Conservations Corps, 1935-1946 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Prisoner of War Camps, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Hurricane, 1937-1940 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Volume No: 41 Connecticut Commission on Forests and Wildlife: minutes, 1925-1943 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Connecticut Park and Forest Commission, 1930-1942 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Volume No: 42A Connecticut Park and Forest Commission, 1942-1943, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Volume No: 42B Connecticut Park and Forest Commission, 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Volume No: 43 [Connecticut Park and Forest Commission]: Farm Forests; State Aid; Forest and Park Association, 1909-1945 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Volume No: 44 Taxation:
    - Connecticut, 1912-1938 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - New Hampshire, 1920-1955 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Maine, 1922-1951 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Volume No: 45A Forest Taxation: A-M (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Volume No: 45B Forest Taxation: M-W (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Volume No: 46 Forest Taxation, 1911-1940 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Tax Inquiry, 1922-1935 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Miscellaneous, 1914-1945 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Volume No: 47 Valuation: Insurance; Stumpage Appraisals, 1909-1946 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Volume No: 48 Valuation: Hiley; Damages, 1909-1940 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Volume No: 49 Louisiana, 1910-1926 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Volume No: 50 Louisiana, 1928-1937 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Volume No: 51 Louisiana: Hardtner; Huey Long, 1911-1952 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Volume No: 52 Minnesota, 1894-1936 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Volume No: 53 Minnesota, 1929-1956 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Volume No: 54 New York, 1905-1945 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Volume No: 55 U.S. Department of "Conservation", Ickes, 1912-1934 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Volume No: 56 U.S. Department of "Conservation", Ickes, 1929-1940 (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Volume No: 57 U.S. Department of "Conservation", 1935-1937 (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Volume No: 58 Quetico-Superior, 1934-1949 (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Volume No: 59 Quetico-Superior, 1924-1946 (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Volume No: 60 Quetico-Superior, 1909-1949 (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - Volume No: 61 Quetico-Superior, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Volume No: 62 Menominee Indians (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - Volume No: 63 Menominee Indians, Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - Volume No: 64 Regulation of Private Forests, 1908-1949 (Box 26, Folder 75)
  - Volume No: 65 Regulation of Private Forests, 1940-1945 (Box 26, Folder 76)
  - Volume No: 66 State Regulation, A - W, 1908-1950 (Box 26, Folder 77)
  - Volume No: 67A Civilian Conservation Corps - Politics, 1933-1934 (Box 27, Folder 78)
  - National Conservation Employees Association, 1937-1938 (Box 27, Folder 78)
  - Volume No: 67B Civilian Conservation Corps - Politics, 1934-1941 (Box 27, Folder 79)
  - Volume No: 68 Pennsylvania, 1906-1936 (Box 27, Folder 80)
  - Volume No: 69 Pennsylvania, 1936-1953 (Box 28, Folder 81)
  - Volume No: 70A Mensuration, 1911-1943 (Box 28, Folder 82)
  - Volume No: 70B Mensuration, 1912-1942 (Box 28, Folder 83)
  - Aerial Photography, 1919-1931 (Box 28, Folder 83)
  - Volume No: 71 Federal vs. State Forests, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 84)
  - Volume No: 72 Forestry Associations, 1910-1954 (Box 29, Folder 85)
  - Park and Wilderness Association (Box 29, Folder 85)
  - Volume No: 73 Professional Ethics, 1922-1938 (Box 29, Folder 86)
  - Volume No: 74 Longleaf Pine, 1923-1940 (Box 30, Folder 87)
  - Hybrid, 1922-1933 (Box 30, Folder 87)
  - Ponderosa Pine, 1921-1951 (Box 30, Folder 87)
  - Farm Forestry, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 87)
  - Volume No: 75 National Parks, 1923-1945 (Box 30, Folder 88)
  - Volume No: 76 National Parks, 1915-1943 (Box 30, Folder 89)
  - Conference on Outdoor Recreation (Box 30, Folder 89)
  - Volume No: 77 National Parks: Olympic, 1935-1953 (Box 31, Folder 90)
  - Volume No: 78 National Parks (Box 31, Folder 91)
    - Rocky Mountain; Grand Canyon; Great Smoky, 1916-1943 (Box 31, Folder 91)
    - Wildlife, 1932-1936 (Box 31, Folder 91)
  - Volume No: 78B Colorado-Big Thompson, 1936-1937 (Box 31, Folder 92)
  - Volume No: 79A Chippewa National Forest, 1881-1945 (Box 31, Folder 93)
  - Volume No: 80 Chippewa National Forest, 1889-1904 (Box 32, Folder 94)
  - Volume No: 81 Chippewa National Forest: Clippings, Photos, 1901-1904 (Box 32, Folder 95)
  - Volume No: 81A Norway Beach Storm, undated (Box 33, Folder 96)
  - Volume No: 82 Forest Service, 1900-1936 (Box 33, Folder 97)
  - Palo Duro, 1906-1934 (Box 33, Folder 97)
  - Swan Valley, 1909-1913 (Box 33, Folder 97)
  - Volume No: 83 State Policies, 1912-1936 (Box 33, Folder 98)
  - Volume No: 84 State Nurseries, 1912-1924 (Box 34, Folder 99)
  - States: A - C, 1908-1952 (Box 34, Folder 99)
  - Volume No: 85 Shelter Belt Project, 1934-1935 (Box 34, Folder 100)
  - Volume No: 86 International Log Rule, 1916-1944 (Box 34, Folder 101)
  - Volume No: 87 Recreational Policy for New England, 1939-1940 (Box 34, Folder 102)
  - Volume No: 88 Selective Logging, 1940-1944 (Box 35, Folder 103)
  - Volume No: 89 States: Maryland, 1907-1956 (Box 35, Folder 104)
  - States: Michigan, 1904-1952 (Box 35, Folder 104)
  - States: Mississippi, 1906-1953 (Box 35, Folder 104)
  - States: Missouri, 1922-1939 (Box 35, Folder 104)
  - Volume No: 90 States: Massachesetts, 1907-1953 (Box 35, Folder 105)
  - Reynolds (Box 35, Folder 105)
  - New England Forestry Foundation, 1944-1952 (Box 35, Folder 105)
  - [New England Forestry Foundation]
    - Volume No: 91 Maine, 1907-1953 (Box 36, Folder 106)
    - Kentucky, 1908-1947 (Box 36, Folder 106)
    - New York, 1938-1953 (Box 36, Folder 106)
    - Volume No: 92 Iowa, 1906-1936 (Box 36, Folder 107)
    - Indiana, 1906-1947 (Box 36, Folder 107)
    - Illinois, 1922-1935 (Box 36, Folder 107)
    - Volume No: 93 Colorado, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 108)
    - Idaho, 1909-1933 (Box 36, Folder 108)
    - Georgia, 1924-1948 (Box 36, Folder 108)
    - Florida, 1921-1946 (Box 36, Folder 108)
    - Delaware, 1912-1937 (Box 36, Folder 108)
    - Volume No: 914 Nebraska, 1906 (Box 36, Folder 109)
    - New Hampshire, 1907-1956 (Box 36, Folder 109)
    - New Jersey, 1906-1956 (Box 36, Folder 109)
    - Volume No: 95 New Mexico - Wisconsin, 1906-1955 (Box 37, Folder 110)
    - Volume No: 96 Oregon, 1909-1955 (Box 37, Folder 111)
    - Washington, 1905-1955 (Box 37, Folder 111)
    - Virginia, Texas, Tennessee, 1908-1941 (Box 37, Folder 111)
    - Volume No: 97 Rhode Island, Vermont, 1908-1956 (Box 37, Folder 112)
  - Volume No: 98 Alaska, 1914-1956 (Box 38, Folder 113)
  - Volume No: 99 Biographies (Box 38, Folder 114)
  - Volume No: 100 Biographies (Box 38, Folder 115)
  - Volume No: 101 Forest Service Policies, 1931-1953 (Box 39, Folder 116)
  - Volume No: 102 Forest Service, 1923-1955 (Box 39, Folder 117)
  - Volume No: 103 National Forests: Management, Regulation, 1909-1956 (Box 40, Folder 118)
  - Volume No: 104 Personal, 1943-1953 (Box 40, Folder 119)
  - Consulting, 1920-1951 (Box 40, Folder 119)
  - Yale Forestry, 1921-1945 (Box 40, Folder 119)
  - Volume No: 105 Schools: Standards, 1947-1952 (Box 40, Folder 120)
  - Schools: Accrediting, 1947-1952 (Box 40, Folder 120)
  - Utilization - New York, 1904-1952 (Box 40, Folder 120)
  - Volume No: 106 American Forestry Association, 1908-1919 (Box 41, Folder 121)
  - Volume No: 107 American Forestry Association, 1920 - 1921 June 30 (Box 41, Folder 122)
  - Volume No: 107A American Forestry Association: Minutes, 1911 March 6 - 1921 May 27 (Box 41, Folder 123)
  - Volume No: 108 American Forestry Association, 1921 July 1 - December 31 (Box 42, Folder 124)
  - Volume No: 109 American Forestry Association, 1923-1956 (Box 42, Folder 125)
  - Volume No: 110 Floods and Erosion (Box 42, Folder 126)
  - Volume No: 111 Long Leaf Pine and Forest Fires in the South, 1931 (Box 43, Folder 127)
  - Volume No: 112 Long Leaf Pine and Forest Fires in the South, 1932 (Box 43, Folder 128)
  - Volume No: 113 Long Leaf Pine and Fires - Illus., 1931 (Box 43, Folder 129)
  - Volume No: 114 Long Leaf Pine and Forest Fires in the South, Vol. 4 (Box 43, Folder 130)
  - Volume No: 115 Long Leaf Pine and Forest Fires in the South, Vol. 5 (Box 43, Folder 131)
  - Volume No: 116 Long Leaf Pine and Forest Fires in the South, Vol. 6 (Box 44, Folder 132)
  - Volume No: 117 International Paper, Ausable Lake and Other Report, 1907-1923 (Box 44, Folder 133)
  - Volume No: 118 Paloduro Canyon, 1904 (Box 44, Folder 134)
  - Blooming Grove, 1911 (Box 44, Folder 134)
  - Volume No: 119 Blooming Grove Hunting and Fishing Club, 1911-1912 (Box 44, Folder 135)
  - Minnesota and Ontario Paper Company, 1925 (Box 44, Folder 135)
  - Volume No: 120 Crossett Lumber Company
    General note
    See: box 52, folder 157
  - Volume No: 121 Reports on Chapin Estate, 1924-1941 (Box 45, Folder 136)
  - Volume No: 122 Reports on Crossett Lumber Company, Arkansas, 1912-1948 (Box 45, Folder 137)
  - Volume No: 123 Grazing photographs (Box 45, Folder 138)
  - Volume No: 123A Long Leaf Pine: La Salle Parish, Louisiana, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 139)
  - Volume No: 124B Accrediting Schools of Forestry, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 140)
  - Volume No: 124C Schools, Accrediting, 1934-1947 (Box 46, Folder 141)
  - Yale Graduates, 1902-1947 (Box 46, Folder 141)
  - Volume No: 125 Lumbering in Minnesota, 1904
  - The Production for Northern Pacific Railroad, 1903 (Box 46, Folder 141)
  - Clippings: History, 1903; 1924 (Box 46, Folder 141)
    See: box 52, folder 158
  - Volume No: 126 New England Forest Practice Survey, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 142)
  - Volume No: 127 Society of American Foresters: Budgets, 1933-1940 (Box 47, Folder 143)
  - Volume No: 128 Society of American Foresters: (Box 47, Folder 144)
    - Elections, 1933-1944 (Box 47, Folder 144)
    - Meetings, 1914-1942 (Box 47, Folder 144)
    - Ethics, 1934-1937 (Box 47, Folder 144)
  - Journal for Society of American Foresters Affairs, 1910-1942 (Box 47, Folder 144)
  - Volume No: 129 Society of American Foresters: Divisions, Sections, Committees, 1933-1941 (Box 47, Folder 145)
  - Volume No: 130 Society of American Foresters: Annual Meeting, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 146)
  - Administration, Council, Executive Secretary, 1934-1935 (Box 48, Folder 146)
  - Volume No: 131 Society of American Foresters: Council, New England Section, 1932-1944 (Box 48, Folder 147)
  - Volume No: 132 Society of American Foresters: Administration, Secretary, 1930-1937 (Box 48, Folder 148)
  - Volume No: 133 Society of American Foresters: Membership Procedure, 1930-1941 (Box 49, Folder 149)
  - Volume No: 134 Society of American Foresters: Policies, 1919-1946 (Box 49, Folder 150)
  - Volume No: 136 Menominee Indians; Chippewa and Superior National Forests; Wilderness Bill; Fire Conference, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 151)
  - Volume No: 137 Menominee Indian Reservation; Quetico-Superior Wilderness Area (Box 50, Folder 152)
  - Volume No: 138 Luther Case (Box 50, Folder 153)
  - Volume No: 139 Liggett, Walter (Box 51, Folder 154)
  - Chapman, H.H.: Correspondence (Box 51, Folder 154)
  - Volume No: 140 Quetico-Superior Memorial Forest, 1944-1946 (Box 51, Folder 155)
  - Volume No: 142 Papers, 1944-1963 (Box 51, Folder 156)
  - Volume No: 120 Crossett Lumber Company (Box 52, Folder 157)
  - Volume No: 125 Lumbering in Minnesota, 1904 (Box 52, Folder 158)
  - The Production for Northern Pacific Railroad, 1903 (Box 52, Folder 158)
  - Clippings: History, 1903; 1924 (Box 52, Folder 158)
  - Publications: index (Box 53, Folder 159)
  - Volume No: I Publications (Box 53, Folder 160)
  - Volume No: II Publications (Box 53, Folder 161)
  - Miscellaneous writings (Box 53, Folder 162)
- CORRESPONDENCE AND TOPICAL FILES, 1897-1963; Series II; 16 linear feet (39 boxes)
  Series II is arranged alphabetically by folder heading.
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series includes two files of grade books, which will be restricted until at least 2020.
  - Alger-Smith lands, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 163)
  - Alignment charts, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 164)
  - Alumni
    See also: box 91, folders 1001-1003
    - General, 1952-1954, undated (Box 54, Folder 165)
    - News articles, 1945-1958, undated (Box 54, Folder 166)
    - Regional correspondence, 1953-1960, undated (Box 54, Folder 167)
  - Rhymes, 1940 (Box 54, Folder 168)
  - Alumni Association: Yale Forestry School
    - General, 1948-1956, undated (Box 54, Folder 169-170)
    - Directory, 1955-1962, undated (Box 54, Folder 171)
    - Elections, 1959-1961 (Box 54, Folder 172)
    - Executive Council, 1917-1958, undated (Box 54, Folder 173-175)
    - Graves Fund, 1955-1957, undated (Box 54, Folder 176)
    - Letters, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 177)
    - MacMillan, H. R., 1956 (Box 54, Folder 178)
    - Notices, 1953, undated (Box 54, Folder 179)
    - Officers, 1956-1960, undated (Box 54, Folder 180)
    - Secretary, 1954-1957, undated (Box 54, Folder 181)
    - Yale Forestry School News, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 182)
      General
      See also: box 91, folder 1010
  - Alumni Board, 1945-1960, undated (Box 54, Folder 183-184)
  - Alumni Fund: Yale Forestry School
    - General, 1952-1959, undated (Box 54, Folder 185)
    - Letter, 1952-1962, undated (Box 54, Folder 186)
    - Records, 1957-1960 (Box 54, Folder 187-191)
    - Records, 1961-1963, undated (Box 55, Folder 192-194)
    - Yale post-graduates, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 195)
  - Alumni occupations, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 196)
  - Alumni Records Office, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 197)
  - Alumni reunions, 1940-1960, undated (Box 55, Folder 198)
  - American Foresters, Society of, 1951-1956, undated (Box 55, Folder 199-200)
    See also: box 81, folders 789-839
  - American Forestry Association
    See also: box 78, folders 691-694
    - General, 1956-1959 (Box 55, Folder 201)
    - Board, 1919 (Box 55, Folder 202)
  - Andrews, E. F., 1917 (Box 55, Folder 203)
  - Animals, birds, wind, and drought, 1931-1955 (Box 55, Folder 204)
  - Association of Class Officers, 1944-1959, undated (Box 55, Folder 205)
  - Association of Consulting Foresters, undated (Box 55, Folder 206)
  - Association on American Indian Affairs, undated (Box 55, Folder 207)
  - Arden, A. J., 1956 (Box 55, Folder 208)
  - Aughanbaugh, J. E., 1951, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 209)
  - Ausable Lake and Mountain Club, 1943 (Box 55, Folder 210)
  - Austin Cary plots, undated (Box 55, Folder 211)
  - Avery, B. F., 1949 (Box 55, Folder 212)
  - Bailey, Robert A., 1958, undated (Box 55, Folder 213)
  - Ballot file, 1949-1950 (Box 55, Folder 214)
  - Balsam, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 215)
  - Bark beetles, 1923-1933 (Box 55, Folder 216)
  - Barron, N. T., 1944-1946 (Box 55, Folder 217)
  - Basal areas, undated (Box 55, Folder 218-219)
  - Beach, David N., 1943-1952 (Box 55, Folder 220)
  - Beard, T. H., 1942 (Box 55, Folder 221)
  - Becton, W. R., 1931-1954, undated (Box 55, Folder 222-223)
  - Behre, C. Edward, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 224)
  - Bennett, John H., undated (Box 55, Folder 225)
  - Besley, Lowell, 1953, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 226)
  - Bibliography, 1940, 1942, undated (Box 55, Folder 227-228)
  - Bickford, C. A., 1938-1945, undated (Box 56, Folder 229)
  - Big longleaf pine, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 230)
  - Big trees, 1945, undated (Box 56, Folder 231)
  - Black Hills fire damage, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 232)
  - Blackwell, Lloyd P., 1956 (Box 56, Folder 233)
  - Board foot standard, 1923-1924 (Box 56, Folder 234)
  - Bogalusa, Louisiana, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 235)
    See also: box 84, folder 842
  - Brown, J. Willcox, 1953 (Box 56, Folder 236)
  - Brown, Nelson C., 1956 (Box 56, Folder 237)
  - Brown, W. Robinson, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 238)
  - Brown Comapny, 1948-1954, undated (Box 56, Folder 239)
  - Brown spot disease, 1922-1944, undated (Box 56, Folder 240)
    See also: box 61, folders 353-354
  - Bull, Coates P., 1948, 1953 (Box 56, Folder 241)
  - C, 1946-1956 (Box 56, Folder 242)
  - California forest: longleaf pine, 1941 (Box 56, Folder 243)
  - Camp Manufacturing Company, 1940-1948, undated (Box 56, Folder 244)
    See also: box 58, folders 283-284
  - Canadian units, 1916-1946 (Box 56, Folder 245)
  - Cannon, Walter B., undated (Box 56, Folder 246)
  - Canterbury, Nathan D., 1950-1957 (Box 56, Folder 247)
  - Cary, Austin, 1923, 1931 (Box 56, Folder 248)
  - Center Church, New Haven, Connecticut, 1945-1960
    See also: box 55, folder 220 box 60, folder 333 box 60, folder 337 box 61, folder 344 box 87, folder 896
    - General (Box 56, Folder 249-256)
    - Building Fund (Box 57, Folder 257)
    - Cabinet (Box 57, Folder 258)
    - "Christ and the Modern World" (Box 57, Folder 259)
    - Council for Social Action (Box 57, Folder 260)
    - Every member canvass (Box 57, Folder 261)
    - Finance Committee (Box 57, Folder 262)
    - Miscellanea (Box 57, Folder 263)
    - Missionary Committee (Box 57, Folder 264)
    - Old Age Home (Box 57, Folder 265)
    - Parish House (Box 57, Folder 266)
    - Parsonage (Box 57, Folder 267)
    - Program (Box 57, Folder 268)
    - Prudential Committee (Box 57, Folder 269)
    - Reception of members (Box 57, Folder 270)
    - Recruiting (Box 57, Folder 271)
    - Stewardship survey (Box 57, Folder 272)
    - Student work (Box 57, Folder 273)
  - Chapman, Bert, undated (Box 57, Folder 274)
  - Chapman, Edmund, 1925-1927, undated (Box 57, Folder 275)
  - Chapman, Ellwood B., 1951 (Box 57, Folder 276)
  - Chapman, Frederick, 1926, 1927, undated (Box 57, Folder 277)
  - Chapman, Herman Haupt, 1940, undated (Box 57, Folder 278)
  - Chapman, Ruth, undated (Box 57, Folder 279)
  - Chapman Forest, 1929-1948, undated (Box 58, Folder 280-281)
  - Charts, undated (Box 58, Folder 282)
  - Chesapeake-Camp Corporation, 1944, undated (Box 58, Folder 283-284)
    See also: box 56, folder 244 box 70, folder 516
  - Chestnut blight, 1925-1936 (Box 58, Folder 285)
  - Chestnut trees, undated (Box 58, Folder 286)
  - Churchill table, 1931-1947 (Box 58, Folder 287)
  - Civilian Conservation Corps, 1933-1940 (Box 58, Folder 288)
  - Clapp, Earle H., 1940 (Box 58, Folder 289)
  - Classification of forest schools, 1934, 1936 (Box 58, Folder 290)
  - Classification of forestry literature, undated (Box 58, Folder 291)
  - Clippings: forestry, 1910-1935 (Box 58, Folder 292-296)
  - Clise Report, 1949-1952, undated (Box 58, Folder 297)
  - Collingwood, G. H., 1942 (Box 58, Folder 298)
  - Committee on Interest Rates, 1923 (Box 58, Folder 299)
  - Computations, undated (Box 58, Folder 300)
  - Conarro, [ ____ ], 1942 (Box 58, Folder 301)
  - Connaughton, Charles A., 1945, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 302)
  - Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1958-1961 (Box 59, Folder 303)
    See also: box 84, folders 847-849
  - Connecticut state parks, 1944-1946 (Box 59, Folder 304-308)
  - Connwood, 1958-1962 (Box 59, Folder 309)
  - Conservation: soil, 1955 (Box 59, Folder 310)
  - Conservation Foundation, 1949, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 311)
  - Continuous inventory, 1949-1950 (Box 59, Folder 312)
  - Conversion factors, 1916-1951 (Box 59, Folder 313)
  - Cord volume table, 1936-1938 (Box 59, Folder 314)
  - Cords, undated (Box 59, Folder 315-316)
  - Cordwood grading, 1933 (Box 59, Folder 317)
  - Correction factors, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 318)
  - Costs of burning, 1942, undated (Box 59, Folder 319)
  - Council of Conservationists, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 320)
  - Cox, William T., 1930, 1931, 1945 (Box 59, Folder 321)
  - Crossett Lumber Company, 1923-1957 (Box 59, Folder 322-323)
  - Crossett Lumber Company, 1952, 1955, undated (Box 60, Folder 324-326)
  - Cruising plan, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 327)
  - Curry, John R., 1958 (Box 60, Folder 328)
  - Cutting practices, 1944-1949, undated (Box 60, Folder 329-330)
  - D, 1948-1958 (Box 60, Folder 331)
  - Data tables, undated (Box 60, Folder 332)
  - Davenport Club, 1944-1947 (Box 60, Folder 333)
  - Daybooks - grades, 1908-1941 (Box 60, Folder 334)
    These records are restricted until January 1, 2020.
  - DBH Crown spread, 1924-1945 (Box 60, Folder 336)
  - Deacons, 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 337)
  - Defenders of furbearers, undated (Box 60, Folder 338)
  - Demerrit, Dwight B., 1951-1952 (Box 60, Folder 339)
    See also: box 74, folder 615
  - Demmon, E. L., 1930-1941 (Box 60, Folder 340)
  - Department of the Interior, 1953-1958
    - General (Box 61, Folder 341)
    - Indians (Box 61, Folder 342)
  - Diagrams, undated (Box 61, Folder 343)
  - Dickerman Fund, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 344)
  - Discount rate, 1950-1955 (Box 61, Folder 345)
  - Dutch elm disease, undated (Box 61, Folder 346)
  - E, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 347)
  - "Early Days in the Ozarks", 1935 (Box 61, Folder 348)
  - Edge, Rosalie, 1943-1948 (Box 61, Folder 349)
  - Egler, Frank, 1952-1956, undated (Box 61, Folder 350-351)
  - Eldredge, Inman F., 1946 (Box 61, Folder 352)
  - Elk Pasture plots, 1931-1948, undated (Box 61, Folder 353-354)
  - Ethics, undated (Box 61, Folder 355)
  - Evans, Berger, 1946-1957 (Box 61, Folder 356)
  - Evans, Charles F., 1948 (Box 61, Folder 357)
  - Even aged plots, undated (Box 61, Folder 358)
  - Extension foresters, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 359)
  - F, 1953-1957 (Box 61, Folder 360)
  - Fair cutting, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 361)
  - Family, 1897, 1927, undated (Box 61, Folder 362)
  - Farm extension, 1924 (Box 61, Folder 363)
  - Farnam, Thomas W., 1927 (Box 61, Folder 364)
  - Federal Land Bank of Springfield, 1923 (Box 61, Folder 365)
  - Field books, 1921-1926 (Box 62, Folder 366-372)
  - Field books, 1927-1933 (Box 63, Folder 373-379)
  - Field books, 1932-1936 (Box 64, Folder 380-386)
  - Field books, 1936-1943 (Box 65, Folder 387-393)
  - Field books, 1942-1947 (Box 66, Folder 394-395)
  - Field trip guide, 1934, 1942 (Box 66, Folder 396)
    See also: box 87, folders 912-913
  - Fire, 1940-1950
    See also: box 59, folder 319 box 76, folders 651-652 box 79, folder 717 box 81, folder 787
    - General (Box 66, Folder 397)
    - Kircher, Joseph C. (Box 66, Folder 398)
    - Kuehn, C. C. (Box 66, Folder 399)
    - Longleaf Pine survival (Box 66, Folder 400-401)
    - Management outline (Box 66, Folder 402)
    - Mattoon, W. R. (Box 66, Folder 403)